嗨  谢尔顿是不是又改了无线网的密码
Hi. Did Sheldon change the Wi-Fi password again?
嗯  现在是"佩妮蹭我们吃的
Yeah, it's "Penny already eats our food.
无线网让她自己装去"
She can pay for Wi-Fi."
没空格
No spaces.
好吧
Okay.
既然你们都阻止不了我来蹭吃的
If you can't get me to stop eating your food,
你凭什么觉得能阻止我蹭无线网呢
what makes you think you can get me to stop using your Wi-Fi?
我相信你还是会浪子回头的
I believe that you're capable of great change.
就像我当初终于让你不再说"情伦节"一样
Like when I finally got you to stop saying "Valentimes Day""
有件很诡异的事儿想听吗
You want to hear something weird?
当然
Sure.
在2000年
In the year 2000,
由黑人组织的一个滑稽篮球队  巡回作表演赛
教皇约翰・保罗二世当选为哈勒姆环球队荣誉队员
Pope John Paul II was named an honorary Harlem Globetrotter.
你这说的都是些啥啊
What are you talking about?
你问佩妮想不想听一些奇怪的事情啊
You asked Penny if she wanted to hear something weird.
没错  因为我有件很诡异的事情要跟她讲
Yeah, because I have something weird to tell her.
我还以为这是个游戏呢
I thought it was a game.
你的怪事是啥
What's yours?
这个哥们儿  吉米・斯贝克曼
There's this guy, Jimmy Speckerman,
当年高中的时候老欺负我来着
who used to torment me in high school.
他在Facebook上给我发了条信息
He sent me a message through Facebook.
他就在本市  想找我喝两杯
He's in town and wants to have drinks.
佩妮  如果这是个游戏  你有如下选择
Okay, Penny, if it were a game, here are your choices.
来自老熟人的一封电邮
An e-mail from an old acquaintance,
还是世界上最大宗教机构的领袖
or the head of one of the largest religious institutions
哈勒姆环球队的队歌
在《Sweet Georgia Brown》的歌声中扣篮  挑一个
in the world slam dunking to "Sweet Georgia Brown." Pick.
选一个吧  不然他不会闭嘴的
Just do it, 'cause he's not gonna let it go.
我选打篮球的教皇
Basketball Pope.
这才靠谱嘛
And that's how it's done.
那个欺负你的家伙你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do about your bully?
-要去见他吗  -不知道啊
- Are you gonna see him? - I don't know.
这就是那个往你的夏威夷潘趣饮料里撒尿的家伙吗
Is this the fellow who peed in your Hawaiian Punch?
不是  那是另外一个
No, that was a different guy.
是不是这个家伙当初提你内裤太过用力
Was he the one who wedgied you so hard,
以至于你一个蛋蛋上提错位
your testicle reascended,
你的整个圣诞节假期
and you spent your whole Christmas break
都在等它慢慢滑下来
waiting for it to come back down?
不是  那又是一个人
No, that was a different, different guy.
那他是不是那个拿你的脑袋敲核桃的家伙
Was he the one who used your head to open a nut?
不是
No.
想到了想到了
Oh, oh, oh.
他是不是那个让你吃自己手毛的家伙
Was he the one who made you eat your arm hair?
不是  不过其实
No, but, actually,
让我吃毛的是这哥们儿的妹妹
that was this guy's sister.
好吧  你觉得他想干嘛呢
All right, well, what do you think he wants?
不知道
I don't know.
你看哈  圣诞假期快到了
You know, the holidays are just around the corner.
也许他想看看能不能
Maybe he wants to see if he can lodge
把另一个蛋蛋也给弄错位了
the other testicle up there.
我都跟你说了  不是这哥们
I told you. That was a different guy.
唉  真可惜  本来可以
Hmm. That's too bad. We could have spent
纽约时代广场新年夜保留节目
零点倒数时会有一个球掉下来
在新年夜等着蛋蛋掉下来的
New Year's Eve waiting for the ball to drop.
■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧原创翻译 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：MADD  Tina  小蛮腰  Joanna
后期：孤帆    时间轴：叶煦
■
校对：Vin  Madd     总监：YY
生活大爆炸  第五季第十一集
凌晨两点钟  你还不睡在干嘛呢
It's 2:00 a.m. What are you doing up?
从斯德哥尔摩直播的诺贝尔颁奖仪式
Nobel Prize acceptance ceremony streaming live from Stockholm.
是啊  你想看看
Sure. You want to see
科学家们今年都爱穿些啥
what all the scientists are wearing this year.
你看看这些人
Look at these men.
他们成功赢得了国际科学界的最高奖项
They've managed to win the top science prize in the world
可是他们对早期宇宙膨胀的
with no more understanding of the quantum underpinnings
量子基础的理解
of the expansion of the early universe
还不如傻子懂得多
than God gave a goose.
你该看看的  莱纳德
You should pay attention, Leonard.
哪天搞不好上台领奖的是你
Someday this could be you up there.
多谢
Thanks.
那你为啥醒了呢
So, what's got you up?
蛤肉吃坏肚子了吗
Did you have a bad clam?
我都没吃蛤肉
I didn't have clams.
我又没有时刻盯着你
I don't watch you 24 hours a day.
谁知道你都干了些啥呢
I don't know what you do.
还不是因为吉米・斯贝克曼的事儿
It's this Jimmy Speckerman thing.
我犹豫到底要不要去见他
I can't decide if I should agree to see him or not.
当然也许是
Of course that might be
因为我上次碰到他的时候
because the last time I ran into him,
他强迫我拿鞋带当牙线用
he made me floss with my own shoelaces.
这次记得穿路夫鞋[没有鞋带]
Wear loafers.
加州大学伯克利分校教授
因观察超新星而发现宇宙加速膨胀获2011年诺贝尔物理学奖
你看看索尔・珀尔马特
Look at Dr. Saul Perlmutter up there,
紧紧地抓着奖杯
clutching that Nobel Prize.
你怎么了啊  索尔
What's the matter, Saul?
怕人偷还是怕人抢啊
You afraid someone's going to steal it?
就像你偷了爱因斯坦的宇宙常数一样一样对吧
Like you stole Einstein's cosmological constant?
你知道吗
You know what?
我受够了总是害怕这家伙了
I am tired of living in fear of this guy.
我要去见他  然后把所有
I'm gonna go see him and finally say
该在高中时告诉他的话都说出来
all the things I should have said in high school.
比如  "找个跟你块头差不多欺负看看"
You know, "Pick on someone your own size"
"你没跟我妈上过床"
"You did not have sex with my mother."
还有"嗯  我还真就知道我为啥在打自己"
And "Yes, I do know why I'm hitting myself."
珀尔马特现在在跟瑞典国王握手了
Oh, now Perlmutter's shaking the king's hand.
小心你的手表哦  国王陛下
Yeah, check for your watch, Gustaf.
没准儿就被他给顺走了
He might have lifted it.
我好喜欢这条裙子
I love this dress.
为啥从来没见你穿过呢
How come I never see you wear it?
因为我一直把它当上衣穿
'Cause when I wear it, it's a shirt.
霍华德今晚在干嘛
So, what's Howard doing tonight?
他们都一起去见那个小时候欺负莱纳德的恶霸了
Oh, they all went with Leonard to confront his childhood bully.
有意思
Oh, terrific.
高中的四分卫对阵四个数学呆子
High school quarterback against four mathletes.
等莱纳德回来的时候
When Leonard gets back,
血清素含量低时更具有攻击性
我想检测一下他体内的血清素水平
I'd love to check his serotonin levels.
你觉得他会让我抽他一管血吗
Do you think he'd let me draw a syringe full of his blood?
他不喜欢针头
Hmm, he's not crazy about needles,
但你要是让他去跑步
but if you get him to go jogging,
他的鼻子就会自动喷血了
it'll just pour out of his nose.
我肯定不敢去见
I don't think I can meet the girl
一直欺负我的人
who was always mean to me.
泰咪・勃妮克
Tammy Bodnick.
有一次上体育课
One time while I was in gym class,
她偷了我的所有衣服
she stole all my clothes
只在我柜子里留了一件精灵装
and left an elf costume in my locker.
太悲剧了
Oh, that's awful.
最悲剧的是  精灵装太大
Worst part was, it was too big.
这不算什么
That's nothing.
九年级的时候  那些女生在我的护手霜里下洛盖尼(生发剂)
In ninth grade, the girls put Rogaine in my hand lotion.
不到六个月  花名就满天飞了
Within six months, the nicknames began to fly.
最伤人的一个应该是猩猩手福勒
I think the one that hurt the most was Gorilla Fingers Fowler.
两个可怜的小姑娘
Wow. You poor thing.
-你呢  -我啊
- What about you? - Oh.
不知道哦  我们学校挺好的
I don't know. I guess my school was a nice place.
没有什么恶霸
We didn't really have bullies.
不是吧  从来没有人给别人取花名
Come on, no one ever gave anyone mean nicknames
捉弄别人  在长毛的指节上粘口香糖
or picked on them or put gum in their hairy knuckles
搞得校医只能用花生酱才能弄下来?
so the school nurse had to use peanut butter to get it out?
没有  我们不会那样
No, we weren't really like that.
我们虽然会戏弄对方
I mean, look, we played pranks on each other,
但都是闹着玩的
but it was never mean.
比如有个女生  凯西・盖格
Like, okay, this one girl, Kathy Geiger,
考试经常得高分  于是我们蒙上她的眼睛
got really good grades, so we blindfolded her,
把她五花大绑到玉米地  留她在那过夜
tied her up and left her in a cornfield overnight.
天啊  太过分了
Oh, my God, that's awful.
才怪  好玩着呢  大家都笑了
No, it was funny. Everyone laughed.
凯西・盖格笑了吗
Did Kathy Geiger laugh?
不知道  很难说
Uh, probably. It's hard to say.
她嘴里塞满了玉米穗
She kind of had an ear of corn in her mouth.
谁能想到
Who would have thought
当年的毛手福勒现在变成恶霸的闺蜜
Fuzzy Fingers Fowler is best friends with a bully?
什么  我才不是恶霸
What? I was not a bully.
可听着感觉你以前是
Kind of sounds like you were.
说不定还是个头头
And maybe a felon.
嘘  你想去玉米地过夜吗
Shh. That's how you wind up in a cornfield.
那边那个是他吗
Is that him over there?
不是
No.
那个呢
How about that guy?
他貌似很恨你
He looks like he'd hate you.
你们其实不用来  我自己能搞定
You know, I can really do this by myself.
兄弟  我们是来挺你的
Hey, we're here to support you, buddy.
才怪  你们只是来看我
No, you're not. You're here to see
会不会被他扯内裤盖到头上
if I get my underwear pulled over my head.
你居然穿内裤来  你个白痴
You wore underwear? You fool.
你想好怎么跟他说了吗
So, have you figured out what you're going to say to him?
废话  他以前在学校这么欺负我
You bet. I am going to make him apologize
我要让我向我道歉
for all the crap he pulled on me in school.
这单子真长
That's quite a list.
我看不懂你写的字
I can't read your handwriting.
这是什么字啊
What's that word?
"阴囊"
"Scrotum."
那这个呢
What's that one?
"钉"
Uh, "Stapled."
莱纳德
Leonard.
嗨
Oh, hi.
我的天哪  老兄  好久不见
Holy crap, man, it's good to see you.
好久不见  吉米  这几位是
Yeah. You, too. Uh, Jimmy, this is
谢尔顿  拉杰  霍华德
Sheldon and Raj and Howard.
你们好  喂  来瓶啤酒
Hi. Fellas... Hey, can I get a beer?
哇  瞧瞧你
Wow. Look at you.
小不点莱纳德・霍夫斯塔德
Little Leonard Hofstadter.
我听说你现在是大科学家了
I hear you're a big-time scientist now.
这就开始讽刺了  真伤人
And there's the first zinger. Ouch.
我现在马马虎虎啦
I'm doing okay, I guess.
不是吧  我在网上看到
Okay? Come on, I read online
你现在是一所大学的物理学家
you're a physicist at a university,
你还得了奖呢
you won some medal.
纽科姆奖
The Newcomb medal.
对  恭喜恭喜
Yeah, congratulations.
恭喜?
Congratulations?
纽科姆奖哦  拜托
The Newcomb medal? Oh, please.
那在科学界相当于
That's the scientific equivalent
小学作业本上得了朵小红花
of a smiley face sticker on your homework.
在我看来挺威风的
From what I read, it sounded like a big deal.
老天  我们就站在这里
Oh, good Lord, are we going to stand here
听他用言语羞辱莱纳德吗
and listen to him tear Leonard apart like this?
喂  我也赢过纽科姆奖
Hey, I won a Newcomb medal, too.
我说得很清楚啦
My point.
你们真该看看这家伙小时候的样子
You should have seen this guy back in the day.
他个子小得  搁哪里都能塞进去
Huh? He was so little, he could fit in just about anywhere.
柜子啦  垃圾桶啦
Lockers, trash cans.
老兄  你怎么钻进那个背包的
Oh, man, how did you get inside that backpack?
功劳不全在我
Oh, I can't take all the credit.
-你可是帮了大忙  -对
- You helped a lot. - Yeah.
咱俩简直就是个搞笑队伍
We were practically a comedy team.
就像黑死病席卷欧洲一样
Like the Black Death and Europe.
吉米  我很好奇你为什么想见我
Jimmy, I'm kind of curious why you wanted to see me.
是这样的
Okay, here it is.
我想到一个绝佳的赚钱点子
I have this great money-making idea.
现在只差一个机械行家来完成
I just need a gear head to get it to the finish line.
严格来说  霍华德才是机械行家
Technically, Howard's the gear head.
莱纳德只是低级的激光操作员
Leonard's just a dime store laser jockey.
什么赚钱点子
What's the idea?
这点子不能外传啊
This is just between us, right?
-行  -好
- Right. - Okay.
你们觉得一副能让任何电影
What do you think about a pair of glasses
变得立体的眼镜怎么样
that makes any movie you want into 3D?
那太帅了
That sounds amazing.
90年代家庭歌舞剧
我第一个要看的电影就是《安妮》
First movie I'm watching-- Annie.
这种眼镜怎么做
How exactly would these glasses work?
我要是知道还用得着找一个书呆子吗
How the hell should I know? That's why I need a nerd.
我觉得这玩意儿行不通
I don't think something like that's even possible.
拜托  你一定有办法的
Aw, come on, you can figure it out.
你是我认识的最聪明的人了
You're like the smartest guy I've ever known.
最聪明的  好吧
The smartest...?! All right,
我可能对挖苦讽刺什么的不在行
you know, I may not have a firm grasp on sarcasm,
可就连我都知道  你该用"出色"而不是"聪明"
but even I know that was a doozy.
莱纳德  你不能永远活在对这个人的恐惧之下
Leonard, you can't live in fear of this man forever.
谢尔顿  我自己能处理
Sheldon, I got this.
你显然不能
You clearly don't.
我这个没骨气的朋友没胆量说的是
What my spineless friend lacks the courage to say
你是一个利用了
is you're a terrible person
他的矮小
who took advantage of his tiny size,
身体协调能力缺乏
his uncoordinated nature and
和先天男子气概缺失的恶人
his congenital lack of masculinity.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
莱纳德  在精神上我还是挺喜欢你的  兄弟
Leonard, I platonically love you, man,
但是请你面对现实  你就是一团糟
but face it, you're a mess.
我都糊涂了
I don't understand.
我想他要说的是  或许在高中时
I think what he's trying to say is that maybe in high school
你有点欺负我
you picked on me a little bit.
有点儿
A little bit?
这家伙把好时之吻巧克力用超能胶粘在你的乳头上
The man super glued Hershey's Kisses to your nipples.
有意思的是  高中时期你的乳头
That's funny because those aren't the kind of kisses
要的可不是巧克力的吻
you want on your nipples.
那张纸是什么
What is that?
这张单子上列满了你对莱纳德做过的可憎行径
This is a list of your heinous acts against Leonard.
其中肯定有一项导致他
One of which is certainly the cause
直到十几岁了还尿床
of him wetting his bed well into his teens.
十四岁不算是  算了
14 is not... Aw, never mind.
这个是什么字
What's this word?
"南希"
"Nancy".
你管我叫"南希"叫了三年
You called me Nancy for three years.
你真该好好练练字了
You really need to work on your penmanship.
天啊  我
Oh, man, I...
我不知道该说什么了
I don't know what to say.
我一直以为我们都乐在其中
I always thought we were just having some fun.
我可一点都乐不起来
It wasn't fun for me.
你用词太客气了  莱纳德
You're being too kind, Leonard.
你把他给毁了
You ruined him.
走吧  伙计们
Come on, guys.
你刚才还真厉害  兄弟
That was pretty badass, dude.
我向来帮助弱者
I help the weak.
又一次证明了我就是蝙蝠侠在世
It's yet another way I'm exactly like Batman.
澄清一下  害我尿床的人不是吉米
Hey, for the record, Jimmy wasn't the reason I wet the bed.
那都是我妈害的
That one has my mother written all over it.
总之我很抱歉
Anyway, I'm really sorry
高中的时候一直笑你口吃
I made fun of your stutter in high school.
你干得很好
You're doing great.
天啊  等她说完费死劲了
Oh, God, just finish the sentence.
好吧  抱歉让你难过了  再见
Okay, well, I'm sorry you feel that way. Bye.
没人想听我道歉
No one wants to hear my apologies.
我认为你不该在电话上道歉
I think your mistake is doing it over the phone.
如果她们能看着你那无辜的大眼睛  铁定会被你融化的
If they could look into your eyes, they'd melt.
佩妮  你过去做过什么都不重要
Penny, it doesn't matter what you did in the past.
重要的是你现在是个好人
You're a good person now.
你说得倒是容易
That's easy for you to say.
别人又没管你叫"婊婊婊婊婊婊子"
You weren't just called a "B-b-b-b-bitch".
也许你可以通过做善事来减轻你的负罪感
Perhaps you could assuage your guilt through altruism.
你是哪个词没听懂
Which word's tripping you up?
"减轻"还是"负罪感"
"Assuage", or "altruism"?
俩都没懂
Both.
通过帮助别人  让你的心好过一点
You'll feel better by doing something nice for someone.
-其实我是懂的  -我从没怀疑过你的实力
- I actually knew that.  - I never doubted you.
每隔一个星期我都会去市中心的一家汤店去帮忙
Every other week I serve at a soup kitchen downtown.
这不行
Ooh, I can't do that.
如果我站在一锅冒热气的汤前  我的头发就会全炸开
If I stand over a steaming pot, my hair just goes boing!
我还能干点别的什么
What else could I do?
还有仁爱之家活动
There's Habitat for Humanity --
给穷人盖房子
building houses for the poor.
拜托  我自己都没有房子
Okay, come on, I don't even have my own house --
又何德何能给别人盖呢
I'm going to build one for someone else?
那捐赠你的一些衣服怎么样
How about donating some of your clothes?
天啊  这太完美了
Oh, my God, that's perfect.
因为我有太多不穿的衣服了
'Cause I have so many clothesI don't wear,
衣橱都装不下了
and they're just taking up space,
我每次逛街还总爱买
and I go shopping to buy more stuff
新衣服都没地方放了
and I have no place to put it.
这下我的麻烦就都解决了
This will totally fix that.
那助人为乐呢
What about helping people?
外加助人为乐
And helping people.
这是你的可可
Here's your cocoa.
-你放的是半脱脂奶不是全脂奶吧  -没错
- Oh, half and half instead of whole milk?  - Yes.
-精确加热到了83.89度了吗  -没错
- Heated to precisely 183 degrees?  - Yes.
正好七块小棉花糖  不多不少吗
Seven little marshmallows, no more no less?
你运气好  多给你一块
You got one for good luck.
我去开门
I'll get it.
我运气好  多给我一块
One for good luck.
这数学水平跟普林斯顿大学有一拼
Must be the kind of math they do at Princeton.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
我来道歉  就用订书机订你的蛋蛋
I want to apologize for...stapling your balls and...
把你脱光了丢进女生更衣室
...throwing you naked in the girls' locker room,
还有把胡萝卜塞到你裤子里向你道歉
stuffing that parrot down your pants.
这个是什么字
What's this word?
-"泻药"  -没错
- "Laxative".  - Oh, right.
初中毕业舞会
Junior prom.
那样做太过分了  伙计
That was not cool, man.
我真的非常非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  我只希望你能原谅我
Yeah. I just hope you can forgive me.
好啊
Yeah.
我想我原谅你了
Sure, I guess.
你真是个大好人
You're a beautiful guy.
谢谢  吉米
Well, thanks, Jimmy.
好了  我该走了
Okay, I got to go.
你还能开车吗
Are you okay to drive?
当然  我喝醉了开得更好
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I drive better drunk.
酒精让人注意力更集中
You know, it makes you pay attention.
不行不行  进来  喝杯咖啡先
No, no, no, come on in. I'll make you a cup of coffee.
-不打扰吗  -不会
- I wouldn't be imposing? - No.
当然会
Yes.
谢尔顿  他现在不能开车
Sheldon, we can't let him drive.
那就拿走他的车钥匙  让他跟其他醉鬼一起
Then take away his keys and make him wander the streets
去大街上游荡去呗
with the other drunks.
刚介绍过的  谢尔顿  拉杰和霍华德
You remember Sheldon and Raj and Howard.
没啥印象
Not really, no.
人生如戏啊  莱纳德
It's funny, huh, Leonard?
学校里  我是赢家你是输家
Back in school, I was the winner and you were the loser.
现在正好相反
And now we're reversed.
你成了赢家
You're the winner.
赢家居然连一杯像样的可可都做不好
You'd think a winner could make a decent cup of cocoa.
-我用下洗手间可以吗  -当然  就在走廊后
- You mind if I use your bathroom? - Yeah, just back there.
感觉如何呀
How about that?
这么多年后  欺负你的高中恶霸
After all these years, your big bad high school bully
终于跟你道歉了
finally apologizes.
真好啊  恢复了我对
Yeah. It kind of rekindles your faith
人性本善的信心
in the basic goodness of people.
知道什么才是真的好吗
You know what would be nice?
什么
What's that?
可以将吉米看作
As a symbolic gesture
多年来欺负我们的所有恶霸的象征
to all the bullies who've tormented us for years,
我们先引狼入室  然后趁他入睡杀了他
we open our home to Jimmy and once he's asleep we kill him.
我是说这样很好  不是说真要这么做
I said it would be nice-- I didn't say we should do it.
我觉得自己就像特蕾莎修女
I feel just like Mother Teresa.
因其一生奉献于解救贫困而获诺贝尔和平奖
除了童贞那部分
Except for the virgin part.
特蕾莎修女是终身职修女 毕生未婚
姐的早就奉献出去了
That ship sailed a long time ago.
我觉得特蕾莎修女会先把衣服洗干净
I think Mother Teresa would have washed the clothes first.
是啊  但愿她去洗衣房
Yeah, well, I bet her laundry room
不用走整整五层楼
wasn't down five flights of stairs.
付出真的比得到更幸福呢
You know, giving really is better than receiving.
我原本以为这是陈词滥调  但现在...
I used to think it was such a cliche, but it seems to be the...
居然有人扔掉这么好的牛仔裤
Look at these cute jeans someone just threw away.
是捐赠
Donated.
没错  捐赠给一个喜欢靴型牛仔裤的可怜女服务生
Yes, to a poor waitress who loves a boot cut.
佩妮
Penny.
拜托  这我穿着绝对赞的呀
Come on, they would be so cute on me...
这裤子配这毛衣整好
They go great with this sweater!
特蕾莎修女可不会...
I don't think Mother Teresa...
这件真漂亮
Oh, that is adorable.
-莱纳德  -什么事
- Leonard. - Yeah.
为防再次留宿别人
In case it comes up again,
那家伙睡在我的位置上了
this right here is an imposition.
那我还能怎么办
What was I supposed to do?
他需要地方过夜
He needed a place to sleep it off.
你太善良了
You're soft.
这世界将把你啃得尸骨无存
This world's going to chew you up and spit you out.
怎么有股炸玉米饼味
When did I have tacos?
早  吉米
Morning, Jimmy.
真的是炸玉米饼味
Oh, there it is, tacos.
我昨晚喝醉了
Man, I tied one on.
是啊
Yeah, you did.
是这样的  我很高兴再见到你
So, uh, listen, it was great to see you again.
还有谢谢你的道歉
And thanks for the apology.
什么道歉
What apology?
你为在学校里对我做的恶作剧道歉啊
For all the crappy stuff you did to me in high school.
天哪  你还在喋喋不休这些事
Geez, you're still harping on that?
真是个娘们
What a puss.
那是我的法式吐司
That's my French toast.
很好吃
It's good.
厨房的事你样样精通嘛  南希
You really know your way around a kitchen, Nancy.
我不想说  我早告诉过你了
I'm not going to say I told you so,
但我们本可以杀了他的
but we could have killed him.
我现在就杀了他
I might kill him right now.
黑暗骑士[蝙蝠侠]挺你
The Dark Knight has your back.
他吓坏了  不过还是挺你
He's scared, but he has your back.
吉米  你该走了
Okay, Jimmy, it's time for you to go.
没问题  等我吃完
Yeah, all right, let me just finish this.
不行  你马上就给我出去
No, you're done. I want you out of my apartment right now.
说得好  神奇小子
Well said, Boy Wonder.
不然怎样
Or what?
别回答  有诈
Don't answer that. It's a trick question.
我可是上过当了
I speak from experience.
我不再怕你了  吉米
I'm not afraid of you anymore, Jimmy.
给我滚出去
Now get out!
你做到了  莱纳德  勇敢反抗了恶霸
You did it, Leonard, you stood up to your bully.
没错  我为自己骄傲
Yeah, I feel pretty good about myself.
你觉得我们跑得过他吗
You think we can outrun him?
我不用跑得过他  只要跑得过你
I don't need to outrun him, I just need to outrun you.
这样做不大好吧
I don't feel good about this.
那就去车里呆着  别熄火
Then sit in the car and keep it running.
你说对了  又有新货到啦
You were right-- a whole new load.
出来吧  瑜伽装  妈妈需要瑜伽上装
Come on, yoga top. Mama needs a new yoga top.
看看吧  伯纳黛特  羊皮靴  你的尺码
Check it out, Bernadette, suede boots, your size.
天哪  真好看
God, they're cute.
为什么要这么好看啊
Oh, why did they have to be cute?
等等  等等  稍等一下
Wait, wait, wait, guys, just hang on.
怎么了  有条子吗
What is it, the fuzz?
看看我们
Look at us.
我们在做什么啊
What are we doing?
我正欢快地跟着你从事犯罪活动
I was gleefully following you to a life of crime,
期待着咱成为牢友的那一天
looking forward to the day we might be cell mates.
不知道伯纳黛特怎么想
I don't know about Bernadette.
我们做错了  都放回去吧
You know, this is wrong. Let's put everything back.
给
Here.
原谅我吧  我给穷人端汤呢
It's okay, I serve soup to poor people!